The best secrets are the hardest to find.
Fountain of Youth is a adventure, fantasy, mystery film directed by Guy Ritchie.
A treasure-hunting mastermind assembles a team for a life-changing adventure.
But to outwit and outrun threats at every turn, he'll need
someone even smarter than he is: his estranged sister.
Luke Purdue, played by John Krasinski.
Charlotte Purdue, played by Natalie Portman.
Esme, played by Eiza González.
Owen Carver, played by Domhnall Gleeson.
Inspector Jamal Abbas, played by Arian Moayed.
Patrick Murphy, played by Laz Alonso.
Fountain of Youth is a 2025 American heist action adventure film
directed by Guy Ritchie and written by James Vanderbilt.
It stars John Krasinski, Natalie Portman, Eiza González, and Domhnall Gleeson, with Arian
Moayed, Laz Alonso, Carmen Ejogo, and Stanley Tucci in supporting roles.
Krasinski and Portman play estranged siblings who team up to embark
on a journey to find the famed Fountain of Youth.
Fountain of Youth was released May 23, 2025, on Apple TV+,
and received mixed reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of egypt, treasure, fountain
of youth, secret organization, heist.
The tone is mind_bending.